Menu

* Resources

* Play

    * * *

### Search

Search only containers

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced search…](https://7cav.us/search/)

Menu

* * *

* * *

Navigation

Install the app

Install

More options

Close Menu

### 7th Cavalry Gaming

#### Join the Tactical Gaming Excellence

* 
    
    Guest, the 7th Cavalry Gaming Regiment is currently **not** accepting Enlistments/Re-Enlistments until after our Furlough (winter break). Enlistments/Re-Enlistments will reopen when we return from Furlough on January 4th, 2025. Please click this [link](https://discord.gg/7cav) to join our Discord server to stay up to date and keep in contact with us!

JavaScript is disabled. For a better experience, please enable JavaScript in your browser before proceeding.

You are using an out of date browser. It may not display this or other websites correctly.  
You should upgrade or use an [alternative browser](https://www.google.com/chrome/).

Help pages

Help
----

Privacy policy
==============

We are 7th Cavalry Gaming ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please contact us.

What information we hold about you
----------------------------------

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

* Your name or username.
* Your email address.
* Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

* You register as a member on this site.
* You fill out our contact form.
* You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
* You fill out fields on your profile.

How your personal information is used
-------------------------------------

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

* For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
* We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
* Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

Other ways we may use your personal information.
------------------------------------------------

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

Keeping your data secure
------------------------

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

Cookie policy
-------------

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on [this page](https://7cav.us/help/cookies).

Rights
------

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please contact us. If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may contact us to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You do not have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please contact us if you wish to discuss specific data deletion queries.

Acceptance of this policy
-------------------------

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

Changes to this policy
----------------------

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

* Change width

[Community platform by XenForo® © 2010-2022 XenForo Ltd.](https://xenforo.com/) Design by: [Pixel Exit](https://pixelexit.com/)

[XenPorta 2 PRO](https://xenforo.com/community/resources/6023/) © Jason Axelrod of [8WAYRUN](https://8wayrun.com/)

* This site uses cookies to help personalise content, tailor your experience and to keep you logged in if you register.  
    By continuing to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies.
